<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>	<title>Alysson's Blog</title>
	<description>The thoughts and feelings of Alys</description>
	<link>https://alysrealm.neocities.org/</link>
	<atom:link href="https://alysrealm.neocities.org/" rel="self"></atom:link>
	<language>en</language>
	<lastBuildDate>
Sat, 26 Oct 2024 23:49:24 +0000
</lastBuildDate>
	<ttl>1440</ttl>

	<item>
		<title>Transparency...</title>
		<description>I titled that like your run-of-the-mill shady influencer, well... because I wanted to. Those people are jokes. But I do have something to get off of my chest! I hope you, dear reader, can find it in your heart to forgive me! sarcastic
I originally was really really drawn to making a site for a few different reasons. One being the endless possiblities (ummm, hello... naming all of my niche interests and thoughts through the gigabytes of stamps and blinkies I have hoarded!!) and well,,, the oth...</description>
		<link>https://alysrealm.neocities.org/posts/2024-09-16-Transparency....html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Transparency...</title>
		<description>I titled that like your run-of-the-mill shady influencer, well... because I wanted to. Those people are jokes. But I do have something to get off of my chest! I hope you, dear reader, can find it in your heart to forgive me! ~~sarcastic~~
I originally was really really drawn to making a site for a few different reasons. One being the endless possiblities (ummm, hello... naming all of my niche interests and thoughts through the gigabytes of stamps and blinkies I have hoarded!!) and well,,, the...</description>
		<link>https://alysrealm.neocities.org/posts/2024-09-16-Transparency....html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Past,Present,Future</title>
		<description>The end of October, 2020 was filled with a lot of trauma, looking back at it.  Doped up on oxycodone, laying on the couch all day, scared and anxious since I was in contact with the hem/onc department... (Being taken up to the office for the first time like I had just been arrested; &quot;Do you know why you're here today?&quot;, in an authorative tone from everyone in the room, parents too. Yes girl! I fucking know what an oncologist is. It's usually what follows a 17 year old girl with a ve...</description>
		<link>https://alysrealm.neocities.org/posts/2024-10-16-past,present,future.html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

</channel>
</rss>